[Music]
fwed is committed to changing the way
people feel about insurance and that's
why it's the first time that there's
been an insurance company that undertook
this kind of partnership to do the
naming rights as FWD insurance is MCX as
more than just an expressway but as a
symbol of the nation's road to progress
the FWD MCX partnership stands as a
symbol of progress where FWD plays a
role in building a more connected and
Progressive Society through financial
protection
so whenever you drive along the whole
stretch of FWD MCX you'll get to see our
story of products partnership and
performance and you're all part of our
mission of financially protecting as
many Filipinos as we can
and today we are thankful that you got
experience FWD in this health and
fashion Space by biking to your heart's
desires
[Music]
FW life insurance has digital and
customer centricity in its DNA in
delivering Financial Protection to all
but having equitably the MCX also serves
as an Innovative link to Filipinos
living in the South we hope that you get
to discover and experience our insurance
product all our products are designed
with the modern Filipino and his future
aspirations
within the ecosystem of fwdmcx
we are present in Alabang and Imus an in
Security Bank our partner in Bank
assurance
[Music]
thanks everyone for celebrating press
play with FWD MCX
[Music]